<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Houston Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="category_landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="spaceCenter_name">Space Center Houston</string>
    <string name="spaceCenter_address">1601 E NASA Pkwy, Houston, TX 77058</string>
    <string name="spaceCenter_contact">https://spacecenter.org/</string>
    <string name="museum_name">Houston Museum of Natural Science</string>
    <string name="museum_address">5555 Hermann Park Dr, Houston, TX 77030</string>
    <string name="museum_contact">http://www.hmns.org/</string>
    <string name="zoo_name">Houston Zoo</string>
    <string name="zoo_address">6200 Hermann Park Dr, Houston, TX 77030</string>
    <string name="zoo_contact">https://www.houstonzoo.org/</string>
    <string name="astrodome_name">Houston Astrodome</string>
    <string name="astrodome_address">8400 Kirby Houston, TX 77054</string>
    <string name="waterwall_name">Gerald D Hines Waterwall Park</string>
    <string name="waterwall_address">2800 Post Oak Blvd Houston, TX 77056</string>
    <string name="_contact">No contact information available</string>
    <string name="bush_name">George H. W. Bush Monument</string>
    <string name="bush_address">Sesquicentennial Park Houston, TX 77002</string>
    <string name="discovery_name">Discovery Green</string>
    <string name="discovery_contact">http://www.discoverygreen.com/</string>
    <string name="discovery_address">1500 McKinney St, Houston, TX 77010</string>
    <string name="eisenhower_name">Dwight D Eisenhower Park</string>
    <string name="eisenhower_address">13400 Aqueduct Rd, Houston, TX 77044</string>
    <string name="eisenhower_contact">http://hcp1.net/Parks/DwightDEisenhower</string>
    <string name="memorial_name">Memorial Park, Houston</string>
    <string name="memorial_contact">http://www.memorialparkconservancy.org/visit-memorial-park.html</string>
    <string name="memorial_address">6501 1/2 Memorial Drive Houston, TX 77007</string>
    <string name="cgbs_name">Chama Gaucha Brazilian Steakhouse</string>
    <string name="cgbs_address">5865 Westheimer Rd, Houston, TX 77057</string>
    <string name="cgbs_contact">+1 (713) 244-9500</string>
    <string name="tot_name">Taste of Texas Restaurant</string>
    <string name="tot_address">10505 Katy Fwy, Houston, TX 77024</string>
    <string name="tot_contact">+1 (713) 932-6901</string>
    <string name="eddie_name">Eddie V\'s Prime Seafood</string>
    <string name="eddie_address">12848 Queensbury Ln, Kirby Drive, Houston, TX 77024</string>
    <string name="eddie_contact">+1 (832) 200-2380</string>
    <string name="uchi_name">Uchi</string>
    <string name="uchi_contact">+1 (713) 522-4808</string>
    <string name="uchi_address">904 Westheimer Rd, Houston, TX 77006</string>
    <string name="saucer_name">Flying Saucer</string>
    <string name="saucer_contact">+1 (713) 228-7468</string>
    <string name="saucer_address">705 Main St, Houston, TX 77002</string>
    <string name="spaceCenter_details">The center features more than 400 space artifacts, permanent and traveling exhibits, attractions and theaters related to the exciting future and remarkable past of America’s human space-flight program – all for one admission price. The experience is designed to engage adults and children alike.</string>
    <string name="museum_details">The mission of the Houston Museum of Natural Science shall be to preserve and advance the general knowledge of natural science; to enhance in individuals the knowledge of and delight in natural science and related subjects; and to maintain and promote a museum of the first class.</string>
    <string name="zoo_details">Over 6,000 permanent animals for whom housing, meals, medical care, and education, are provided! There are over 2 million guests each year who come to experience incredible variety of animals and ecosystems, as well as attend special private and public events and entertainment. Dedicated staff work around the clock to ensure that the Zoo is always running smoothly for the safety and well being of our residents and guests.</string>
    <string name="astrodome_details">The NRG Astrodome, also known as the Houston Astrodome or simply The Astrodome, is the world\'s first multi-purpose, domed sports stadium, located in Houston, Texas. Construction on the stadium began in 1962, and it officially opened in 1965.</string>
    <string name="waterwall_details">The Gerald D. Hines Waterwall Park, formerly the Williams Waterwall and the Transco Waterwall, is a multi-story sculptural fountain that sits opposite the south face of Williams Tower in the Uptown District of Houston.</string>
    <string name="bush_details">Located in Sesquicentennial Park, the garden features an eight-foot bronze sculpture of  former president George H. Bush by artist Chas Fagan of Charlotte, North Carolina and a semicircular wall of four bas-reliefs by Houston artist Wei-li \"Willy\" Wang that depict President Bush as a Navy pilot in World War II; as a Houston oilman and member of Congress; with Mikhail Gorbachev in managing the peaceful end of the Cold War; and with wife Barbara attending the Inaugural of their oldest son as 43rd president.</string>
    <string name="discovery_details">Discovery Green is a beautiful, vibrant 12-acre park in the heart of downtown Houston that opened to the public in April 2008. The park was envisioned by several committed Houston philanthropists, who saw the space as a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to create an urban park that would redefine the landscape of downtown. In less than four years, the site that became Discovery Green was transformed from an undeveloped, concrete eyesore into a beautiful and vibrant destination adjacent to the George R. Brown Convention Center.</string>
</resources>
